I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single night and I'm still able to
maintain a caloric deficit. Here are
some of the pints I made this week to
stay fit and smash my protein goal. That
first one was a cookie butter flavor
cookie butter base with biscott pieces
mixed in. Staying on that cinnamon
theme, this is cinnamon pebbles, which
is a new cereal from the Pebbles team
that is basically just Rice Krispies
with cinnamon sugar on them. Mix that
into a cinnamon base. Absolutely
delectable. Here's one of my most
nostalgic flavors, Rocky Road. This is a
chocolate base with mini dehydrated
marshmallows mixed in as well as
almonds. You get the sweetness, the
crunch, and the richness from the
chocolate. Now, this is one that took a
lot of testing. This is key lime pie.
It's pretty hard to mix acid and milk,
as I'm sure a lot of you know. And you
were not going to see me using that
disgusting lime Jell-O mix. If you guys
see a recipe using that, just know it's
going to suck. Then I did cake batter
Oreo. This reminded me a lot of a cold
stone flavor. It was just cake batter
ice cream with Oreos mixed in, but kind
of just gave me that Cold Stone crearyy
vibe. Then I ended off the week with
cookies and cream. Basically just a
protein shake plus Oreos. Super easy,
but super delicious. What flavor should
I make